A Guide to the Shenandoah Valley Business Papers
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #4505
Shenandoah Valley Business Papers 1881-1924
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
4505
ca. 100 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift 1953 October 30
Scope and Content
The following material concerns businesses in which N. F. Snarr had an interest, including the Farmers Mutual Telephone System and three general stores: Borden Brothers; Snarr, Borden and Miley and Snarr and Miley Company. Many of the ledgers and account books were not labeled so the store to which they belong could not be determined.
Container List
- Farmers Mutual Telephone System of Shenandoah: Ledger, 1904-1909 (Box Box 1)
- Farmers Mutual Telephone System of Shenandoah: Ledger, 1910-1916 (Box Box 1)
- Farmers Mutual Telephone System of Shenandoah: Annual Reports, 1910,1911,1914 (Box Box 1)
- Farmers Mutual Telephone System of Shenandoah: Letter File, 1923-1924; (4 folders) (Box Box 1)
- Day Book (possibly for Snarr, Borden and Miley General Store), 1902-1906 (Box Box 2)
- Day Book (as above), 1906-1907 (Box Box 2)
- Day Book (as above), 1908-1909 (Box Box 2)
- Day Book (as above), 1909 (Box Box 2)
- Day Book (as above), 1910-1911 (Box Box 2)
- Day Book (as above), 1911-1912 (Box Box 2)
- Day Book (as above), 1913-1914 (Box Box 2)
- Day Book (as above), 1914-1914 (Box Box 2)
- Day Book (as above), 1914 (Box Box 2)
- Day Book (as above), 1916 (Box Box 2)
- Day Book (as above), 1916 (Box Box 2)
- Day Book (as above), 1917-1918 (Box Box 2)
- Day Book (as above), 1918-1920 (Box Box 2)
- Ledger: Fertilizer Sales, 1888-1890 (Box Box 3)
- Ledger: Fertilizer Sales, 1891-1894 (Box Box 3)
- Ledger: Fertilizer Sales, 1898-1902 (Box Box 3)
- Day Book with list of phosphate purchases, 1904-1906 (Box Box 3)
- Day Book, 1907-1910 (Box Box 3)
- Day Book, 1910-1913 (Box Box 3)
- Day Book and fertilizer account book (Box Box 3)
- Journal labeled no.2, 1897-1899 (Box Box 4)
- Journal labeled no.3, 1899-1900 (Box Box 4)
- Journal labeled no.4, 1899-1900 (Box Box 4)
- Journal labeled no.7, 1901-1902 (Box Box 4)
- Journal labeled no. 10, 1907-1910 (Box Box 4)
- Journal, 1911-1914 (Box Box 5)
- Inventory book for Borden Bros., 1881 (Box Box 5)
- Ledger of J.S. Borden and Co., 1888-1891 (Box Box 5)
- Account book: "Notes and Obligations due Snarr, Borden and Miley", 1891-1903 (Box Box 5)
- Account Book, 1894-1907 (Box Box 6)
- Journal, 1904-1907 (Box Box 6)
- Account Book labeled "Commission Book", 1904-1913 (Box Box 6)
- Wholesale Account Book: Snarr and Miley, 1907-1918 (Box Box 7)
- Account Book, 1908-1910 (Box Box 7)
- Account Book, 1908-1917 (Box Box 7)
- "Bark Book" (includes mostly misc. figures), 1910 (Box Box 7)
- Inventory Book, 1912 (Box Box 7)
- Inventory Book of Snarr and Miley, 1918 (Box Box 7)
- Account Book, 1918 (Box Box 7)
- Unidentified miscellaneous papers, notebooks, n.d. (Box Box 7)